wealthcreatorsuniversity.com 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy

**www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com  **

**Privacy statement**

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com is a subsidiary of Financial Office Marketing Group (Pty) Ltd.  Wealth Insights is the official e-newsletter of the group.

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com values the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information handling practices.

Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club operates businesses, retail stores and Web sites under the name Senbiz. If you provide information to any of the above businesses, stores or Web sites, this information may be combined or shared between current or future Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club entities and subsidiaries.

Although our businesses, stores and Web sites have unique services and offerings, they share a similar privacy philosophy. Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club follows these privacy principles in our conduct in the collection, use, release and security of customer information both online and offline:

  * Giving you CHOICES about how your data will be used.

  * Providing you NOTICE of our information practices.

  * Providing you the opportunity to UPDATE or CORRECT your personal information.

  * Using information SECURITY safeguards.

  * Limiting the SHARING of your information.

  * Committing to COMPLYING with applicable privacy requirements.

  * Providing you with means to CONTACT US about privacy-related issues.

Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club. may modify its privacy policy as needed consistent with these principles.   

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com  takes your privacy seriously, which is why we have created the following policy for your protection and security. Please read it carefully.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy ("The Policy") covers www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com collects when you are on the www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com site, and when you use www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com's services.

The policy also covers www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com's business partners share with www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com or that www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com may collect on a partner's site.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com does not own or control, or to people that www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com  does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com newsletter - also calls The Wealth Insights Newsletter - or free report, submit feedback or sign on as a member of the www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com  community. www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners in The Dr Hannes Dreyer Group.

When you register as a member of the www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com and the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club community, we ask for your name, email address, and country of origin. Once you register with www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com  and sign in to our Wealth Creators Club community, you are not anonymous to us.

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP Address, www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com cookie information, and the page you requested.

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com uses information for four general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to contact you about specials and new products and to send you the regular Wealth Insight Newsletter 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com and therefore the_ Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club community _will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone._

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com and the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club community will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
  * We respond to a compulsory court order to comply with due legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com Rules - or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

* * *

**Right of Access**

The Wealth Creators University prides itself with regards to the results achieved by its students directly related to the education provided by the university, as well as the implementation of the principles and strategies by its Students. The Wealth Creators University is therefore not suitable for all, and therefore uses stringent criteria to accept prospective students. To become part of the Wealth Creators University you will need to complete and submit an application and complete an acceptance test, as well as be willing to implement the principles and strategies taught. Additionally all applications are subject to approval by the directors of the Wealth Creators University. The directors of the Wealth Creators University reserves the right of access.

**Non Disclosure Agreements**

The Wealth Creators University education is based on sound principles and strategies which is fully tested and therefore guaranteed by the university itself. As a result of the vast amount of intellectual property  that are shared to students during the events of the Wealth Creators University, it is required of all students to agree to our non-disclosure agreement before enrolling for any Wealth Creatos University course. The non-disclosure agreement does not prevent students to share their successes or failures, but prevents sharing without permission any material shared to them by the Wealth Creators University and any of its related educational ventures.

* * *

**Cookies**

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com may set and access www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data - which often includes an anonymous unique identifier - that is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. The way other companies use their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com 's cookies.

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com products and services. Web pages may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or "web beacon") that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

You may change or update the information you have supplied www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com or the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club community at any time. Please use the editing facilities available from your account page to do this.

**Security**

Every effort is made to keep your information private and away from hackers. However, it is not possible for us to guarantee your privacy. You should weigh up the risk that your details will be misused by hackers with the benefit of receiving the great information that this site has to offer.

**Whom can I CONTACT if I have questions or concerns?**

Please contact our Privacy Manager to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit privacy-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days. You may contact us in the following ways:

Postal Mail:  
Wealth Creators University  
Attn: Privacy Manager  
PO Box 60942  
Karenpark

Email: [webservices@WealthCreatorsUniversity.com](mailto:webservices@WealthCreatorsUniversity.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement)  
Phone:+27 (0)12 542 4560

**Will this Privacy Policy CHANGE?**

Because our Web sites will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we provide, this policy is subject to change. If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here or in other formats we deem acceptable, so that you will always know what information we collect online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. If we change our information practices or this Privacy Policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a different manner, we will give you the choice to opt-out of having your past information used or shared in that new manner.

**Last revision date:** Nov 30, 2010  
www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com has reviewed and rewritten its Privacy Policy to (1) make it easier to read and understand, (2) describe its practices in better detail, (3) make it clear that we may combine or share the information we hold across all current or future the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club community, and (4) combine privacy policies and practices for the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club retail stores and its affiliates. Instead of having multiple and potentially conflicting privacy policies for the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club entities and our Web sites, we have decided to ensure all the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club entities operations follow the same privacy standards. By combining our privacy policies and practices, we give our customers the same privacy standards whether providing the Dr Hannes Dreyer’s Wealth Creators Club personal information on or offline. If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, email our Privacy Manager at [webservices@WealthCreatorsUniversity.com](mailto:webservices@WealthCreatorsUniversity.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement). 

www.WealthCreatorsUniversity.com may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
